<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidBeginners</string>

    <string name="overview_frozen">
        Anna sets out on a journey with an iceman, Kristoff, and his reindeer, Sven, in order to
        find her sister, Elsa, who has the power to convert any object or person into ice.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_moana">
        Moana, daughter of chief Tui, embarks on a journey to return the heart of goddess Te Fitti
        from Maui, a demigod, after the plants and the fish on her island start dying due to a blight.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_the_boss_baby">
        Seven-year-old Tim gets jealous when his parents give all their attention to his little
        brother. Tim soon learns that the baby can talk and the two team up to foil the plans of
        the CEO of Puppy Co.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_tangled">
        Rapunzel, a naive and young girl, is locked up by her overly protective mother. Her wish to
        escape into the world outside finally comes true when she meets the good-hearted thief, Flynn.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_despicable_me">
        Gru, a criminal mastermind, adopts three orphans as pawns to carry out the biggest heist in
        history. His life takes an unexpected turn when the little girls see him as their potential
        father.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_kung_fu_panda">
        When Po the Panda, a kung fu enthusiast, gets selected as the Dragon Warrior, he decides to
        team up with the Furious Five and destroy the evil forces that threaten the Valley of Peace.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_toy_story">
        Toy Story is a 1995 American computer-animated comedy film produced by Pixar Animation
        Studios and released by Walt Disney Pictures. The first installment in the Toy Story
        franchise, it was the first entirely computer-animated feature film, as well as the first
        feature film from Pixar.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_wall_e">
        A machine responsible for cleaning a waste-covered Earth meets another robot and falls in
        love with her. Together, they set out on a journey that will alter the fate of mankind.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_up">
        Carl Fredricksen, a 78-year-old balloon salesman, is about to fulfill a lifelong dream.
        Tying thousands of balloons to his house, he flies away to the South American wilderness.
        But curmudgeonly Carl\'s worst nightmare comes true when he discovers a little boy named
        Russell is a stowaway aboard the balloon-powered house.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_the_incredibles">
        Forced to adopt a civilian identity and stuck in a white-collar job, Mr Incredible itches
        to get back into action. When he is lured into a trap by the evil Syndrome, his family
        contrives to save him.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_ice_age">
        Manny the mammoth, Sid the loquacious sloth, and Diego the sabre-toothed tiger go on a
        comical quest to return a human baby back to his father, across a world on the brink of
        an ice age.
    </string>

    <string name="overview_finding_nemo">
        Nemo, an adventurous young clownfish, is unexpectedly taken from his Great Barrier Reef
        home to a dentist\'s office aquarium. It\'s up to his worrisome father Marlin and a friendly
        but forgetful fish Dory to bring Nemo home — meeting vegetarian sharks, surfer dude turtles,
        hypnotic jellyfish, hungry seagulls, and more along the way.
    </string>
    <string name="search_movie_name">Search</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>